(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[3],{Nr18:function(e,t,a){"use strict";var n=a("S/j/"),s=a("d/Gc"),o=a("ne8i");e.exports=function(e){for(var t=n(this),a=o(t.length),r=arguments.length,i=s(r>1?arguments[1]:void 0,a),l=r>2?arguments[2]:void 0,c=void 0===l?a:s(l,a);c>i;)t[i++]=e;return t}},Ugz3:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"questions":[{"question":"Do you have key performance indicators (KPIs) to help measure whether or not you’re meeting all of your business objectives (safety, production, quality, consumer safety, costs, etc.)?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We have no key performance indicators (KPIs) to track whether or not we’re meeting our business objectives."},{"val":3,"text":"We have KPIs for some business objectives, but not for all."},{"val":2,"text":"We have KPIs, but only management is fully aware of them."},{"val":1,"text":"We have and actively reference KPIs to track whether or not we’re meeting business objectives. "},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"Is your organization able to anticipate and adapt to emerging business trends and new market developments?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"There’s no need for that kind of agility in our industry."},{"val":3,"text":"Coordinating change between Maintenance and Operations teams is difficult."},{"val":2,"text":"Our culture is adaptable, but asset criticality must be reassessed to reprioritize anytime we need to change course."},{"val":1,"text":"We have a culture that can adapt to change, backed by streamlined processes, a single source of data, and digital collaboration across departments."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"Are priorities for assets clearly defined, communicated, and tracked across your organization?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We do not have a full view of what our workforce is doing or how they prioritize. Instead, we rely on our department managers to manage priorities."},{"val":3,"text":"We have a collaborative working culture with clear metrics, priorities, and reporting mechanisms."},{"val":2,"text":"We have ranked all of our assets based on criticality, and we have developed deliberate maintenance packages. Our team works according to risk-based priorities."},{"val":1,"text":"We have a single, integrated data hub that provides us with the current live status of our assets’ performance. We can visualize KPIs, actions, and next steps throughout our plant(s)."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"Is your resource utilization (contractors, people capacity, skills, spare parts, etc.) optimally balanced against plant performance?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"Our organization lacks overall insight into forecasts, actual costs, and resource usage. There is a high correction rate every month."},{"val":3,"text":"Our cost accounting systems tell us where we are with the overall running costs, but we struggle to get control over budgeting and periodic forecasts."},{"val":2,"text":"Our cost structures provide us with full insight into where money and resources go, but various factors still prevent us from being more predictable and accurate."},{"val":1,"text":"Our resources are allocated and reported through streamlined processes and supported by a single ERP/EAM system. We can balance this against operational risks and actual asset performance to find and resolve differences."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"How do you balance differences between OPEX and CAPEX for your asset base?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We have not assessed overall asset condition against our financial plans. We only refer to cost information at the most general levels."},{"val":3,"text":"Our engineers have a replacement project list, but we have not integrated this insight into our asset life cycle and performance alongside financial reporting."},{"val":2,"text":"We have aligned the assessment of our asset base against our financial planning, current performance, and CAPEX projections for the replacement and refurbishing of end-of-life equipment."},{"val":1,"text":"We have an integrated asset evaluation process and can predict and prioritize our CAPEX/OPEX investment against various risk-based scenarios."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure.}"}]},{"question":"When it comes to asset performance and optimization, how do you know if your operations and maintenance teams are effectively using data and collaborating?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We are still working in silos, with each team focusing on their specialized areas, and not working across departmental borders yet."},{"val":3,"text":"We share a lot of information and communicate effectively around production schedules and maintenance slots, but our processes and data are not connected across different departments."},{"val":2,"text":"We have structured our data and streamlined our processes, but our systems do not efficiently support and accelerate our workforce."},{"val":1,"text":"We use an integrated digital solution that enables our departments to efficiently access a single data source and work with our assets."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"How do you close the feedback loops in your processes to understand whether your technical workforce is doing the right things, the right way?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We have an experienced workforce and trust that they know what the right actions are for any given asset."},{"val":3,"text":"We have made an inventory of the roles and profiles needed in our organization and have a learning plan to transfer and update knowledge across the team."},{"val":2,"text":"We evaluate our business processes and workforce capabilities from the ground up to develop KPIs for workforce productivity and operational efficiency."},{"val":1,"text":"We share and structure knowledge around our assets and their failure behavior in our systems. Based on integrated digital data, we can detect knowledge gaps in the team as they arise and define prescriptive work packages to support our people."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"How do you measure the condition of your physical assets?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"Our expert workforce understands the status of our equipment and the tasks required to maintain it."},{"val":3,"text":"We have data that shows how often some of our key assets fail and what the business consequences are. We evaluate that data periodically and combine it with other data from Operations, Quality, and Safety departments to understand the asset’s operating window."},{"val":2,"text":"We have established an integrated process that records deviations in performance and detects repeated problems across the plant. This information is combined with regular visual walkdowns and deep dives into structural performance problems and major events."},{"val":1,"text":"We have systems that capture and record operations and maintenance data on our key assets, combining it with smart analytics so that we have a complete view of the asset’s performance, from engineering to operations and maintenance."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"Can your organization provide the right data in various supply chain and operational scenarios for informed decision making?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We replace, modify, and extend our asset base using assumptions about their useful life, capacity constraints, and our broader product portfolio."},{"val":3,"text":" We’ve got some insight into the performance potential of our existing assets and we drive improvement initiatives to make full use of the assets we have."},{"val":2,"text":"aWe have insight into the risk profile of each of our assets and the life cycle phase it’s in to determine whether to extend a critical asset’s operational lifetime, replace it, or implement new technologies."},{"val":1,"text":"We benefit from a complete overview of our asset portfolio using risk profile, life cycle distribution, and uniform asset health indicators."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"How easily can you predict the behavior of your current assets?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We can’t predict failures. Our organization maintains our assets on a reactive basis."},{"val":3,"text":"We know our weak spots based on experience. We trust our workforce to prevent failures before they occur."},{"val":2,"text":"We have information on fact-based failure patterns of our key assets, gathered as a result of monitoring and registration of past incidents. We analyze and log root causes properly and proactively work on mitigating problems."},{"val":1,"text":"We apply enhanced AI methodologies to predict potential failures before they occur."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"How do you know if your engineering workforce and your EPC partners are designing assets to drive optimal performance across their life cycle?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We rely on a very capable Engineering department and EPC contractors to design the best possible assets."},{"val":3,"text":"We have defined clear technology portfolios by facility type, and our design team and EPCs must comply with these criteria when designing new facilities or modifying brownfield sites."},{"val":2,"text":"We have established clear technology and engineering protocols that underpin the designs of each of our plants. We deliberately match our standardized technical solutions and asset templates to these design and operating protocols, supported by all required documentation."},{"val":1,"text":"We have an integrated process that spans from concept definition to operations handover and accounts for historical asset performance and operational data design decisions."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"Is the information in your systems accurate, complete, and synchronized with the physical asset?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"The data in our systems is not complete or accurate enough for us to allocate and monitor activities throughout the plant."},{"val":3,"text":"The data in our systems is accurate and complete but divided into different systems."},{"val":2,"text":"We have defined processes and systems that reflect our physical plant in every way. We rely on our teams to keep data accurate and up to date."},{"val":1,"text":"We have a fully integrated hub of centralized data. New data is fed into the hub via an automated process from multiple sources. Everyone on the team has real-time access to this data."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"How do you ensure asset sustainability in your operations?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We strive to reduce our overall energy footprint, but we do not have clearly defined KPIs for sustainability around our assets."},{"val":3,"text":"We have KPIs to drive improvement projects and boost sustainability as part of our business planning."},{"val":2,"text":"We have a strategy in place based on a sustainability footprint per asset. We have specific targets and monitor our success using clearly defined KPIs that are shared with the whole team."},{"val":1,"text":"We use digital data and monitoring tools on an integrated platform to track our sustainability efforts and performance across every aspect of the asset life cycle."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"Do you know the long-term benefits and ROI of your digital initiatives up front?","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"We haven’t started our digital journey yet."},{"val":3,"text":"We have initiated several pilot projects to explore the benefits of digitalization, but ROIs are not always clear."},{"val":2,"text":"We have defined a clear business goal per digital initiative, set clear success criteria, and measure ROIs as we go. We periodically report the outcomes to management."},{"val":1,"text":"We have created a digital roadmap that outlines our desired business objectives. All initiatives follow a shared strategy, aggregating the outcomes at the appropriate business levels."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]},{"question":"Select the option that best describes your company’s perspective on digital transformation.","answers":[{"val":4,"text":"Our culture isn’t as open to digital transformation as we would like."},{"val":3,"text":"We use general best practices for change management when we implement new systems across our organization. We build training plans and keep everyone informed on how the new system works and how to use it."},{"val":2,"text":"We create a custom change management process for everyone in the team who will be affected by a digital initiative. We use professional cultural awareness programs and change management tools to ensure change is adopted and the benefits are clear to everyone."},{"val":1,"text":"We drive and measure our culture to support new digital technologies. Our people understand the importance of digital culture and are actively working on the adoption of an open technology approach."},{"val":0,"text":"I’m not sure."}]}]}')},bHtr:function(e,t,a){var n=a("XKFU");n(n.P,"Array",{fill:a("Nr18")}),a("nGyu")("fill")},"fOM+":function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a("q1tI"),s=a.n(n),o=(a("wcMv"),a("Bl7J")),r=(a("bHtr"),function(e){return s.a.createElement("section",{className:"progress-wrapper"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress",style:{width:e.fill+"%"}}))}),i=(a("f3/d"),function(e){return s.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",name:""+e.name,value:e.value,className:"form-check-input",onChange:function(t){return e.selected(t,e.value,e.radioid)},checked:e.checked===e.radioid})}),l=function(e){var t;return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer"},s.a.createElement(i,((t={name:e.name,selected:e.selected,value:e.value,checked:e.checked,radioid:e.radioid}).selected=e.selected,t)),s.a.createElement("p",null,e.text))},c=a("Ugz3"),u=a("Wbzz"),d=function(e){return s.a.createElement("nav",null,0===e.question?s.a.createElement(u.a,{to:"/",className:"cta back",disabled:e.active,onClick:function(t){return e.handleNav("b")}},"Intro"):s.a.createElement("button",{className:"cta back",onClick:function(t){return e.handleNav("b")}},"Back"),14===e.question?s.a.createElement(u.a,{to:"/results",state:{result:e.result,resultcontent:e.content},className:"cta",disabled:e.active,onClick:function(t){return e.handleNav("n")}},"Results"):s.a.createElement("button",{className:"cta",disabled:e.active,onClick:function(t){return e.handleNav("n")}},"Next"))};var h=function(e){var t,a;function n(t){var a;return(a=e.call(this,t)||this).handleAnswer=function(e,t,n){var s=a.state.question,o=a.state.score.slice();o[s]=t,a.setState({score:o,isActive:!1,checked:n})},a.calcPercentage=function(e,t){return 100*e/t},a.calcTotal=function(e){e.reduce((function(e,t){return e+t}),0)},a.handleResult=function(){var e=a.state.total;return e>=0&&e<=15?0:e>=16&&e<=25?1:e>=26&&e<=40?2:e>=41&&e<=60?3:void 0},a.handleNav=function(e){var t=a.state.question,n=t-1,s=t+1;if("b"===e&&t>0)a.setState({question:n,progress:a.calcPercentage(t-1,15),checked:null});else{if(!("n"===e&&s<15))return!1;a.setState({question:s,progress:a.calcPercentage(t+1,15),isActive:!0,total:a.state.score.reduce((function(e,t){return e+t}),0),result:a.handleResult(),checked:null})}},a.state={question:0,score:[],total:0,progress:0,isActive:!0,checked:null},a}return a=e,(t=n).prototype=Object.create(a.prototype),t.prototype.constructor=t,t.__proto__=a,n.prototype.render=function(){var e=this,t=c.questions[this.state.question];return s.a.createElement(o.a,null,s.a.createElement(r,{fill:this.state.progress}),s.a.createElement("article",{className:"container--assessment"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-sm-12 col-md-3 left"}),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-sm-12 col-md-9 right"},s.a.createElement("p",{className:"question"},t.question),t.answers.map((function(t,a){return s.a.createElement(l,{key:a,radioid:e.state.question+"-"+a,value:t.val,text:t.text,selected:e.handleAnswer,checked:e.state.checked,name:"question-"+e.state.question})})),s.a.createElement(d,{question:this.state.question,handleNav:this.handleNav,result:Math.round(this.state.total/60*100),content:this.handleResult(),active:this.state.isActive}))))))},n}(n.Component);t.default=h}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=component---src-pages-assessment-js-4c4cfdb98a5f18294c40.js.map